
const tasks = [
  {
    sentence: "Chicagoans forward their clocks by one hour during spring which is referred to as daylight savings time.",
    question: "How many hours ahead are Chicago's clocks in spring?",
    answers: ["Two", "One"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    sentence: "Thailand is know as the land of white elephant because the thai royal family owns elephants with lighter skin color.",
    question: "What is another name for Thailand?",
    answers: ["Land of grey elephant", "Land of white elephant"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    sentence:
      "The kilobyte is recognized as being the smallest unit of memory while the largest unit of memory is the yottabyte.",
    question: "Which unit of memory is the smallest",
    answers: ["Kilobyte", "Byte"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    sentence:
      "Researchers discovered that classical music helps plants grow better and faster.",
    question: "Does electronic music help plants grow better and faster?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    sentence: "Diamonds are the hardest rocks found in the world while talc is the softest rock in the world.",
    question: "Is talc the hardest rock found in the word?",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    sentence:
      "Our nails, hair strands and outer layer of the skin are made of a substance called keratin.",
    question: "Which substance makes the outer of the skin?",
    answers: ["Keratin", "Cells"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    sentence:
      "England used eels as currency for rental agreements in medieval times.",
    question:
      "What currency was used in medieval England in rental agreements?",
    answers: ["Eels", "Guilders"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    sentence: "Poland is the original creator of bagels.",
    question: "Where did bagels orignate from?",
    answers: ["Holland", "Poland"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    sentence: "A seismologist studies earthquakes and geological materials.",
    question: "People who study earthquakes are called?",
    answers: ["Seismologists", "Qualogists"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    sentence: "Morroco has a red flag with the greenest star ever in the middle",
    question: "Does Morroco have a red flag with a blue star in the middle?",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
